OK, welcome to our AdultWork
101 call. So hopefully we'll go over some useful things today for
you about our host site, AdultWork. And you'll have a chance to just ask us any
questions. If there's anything about the site that you're unsure of, then yeah, we're
happy to answer any questions as well. So AdultWork is our
host platform. And so it's useful to get to know how to make the most out of it for
your business. The information we'll talk about today is to the best of our knowledge
as the platform changes and updates quite often.
So please check with a mentor if you're struggling or unsure about anything.
We'll also occasionally post updates in the groups and things if there's something
that's changed, but there are quite a few updates.
So yeah, we'll do it to the best of our knowledge today.
Also just to mention, our dream here at the ethical community is to have our own
platform. So we'd love to have our own platform based on our own ethics, safety,
and transparency. But for now, we've got to navigate this side of the platform together.
And it doesn't always reflect our own values, but we do the best we can to make the
most of it. So we're there with you. We're also camming on this site and camming across
some difficulties with it now and again. But we're here to support you, and we're
working with you as well. So how much you learn about the site and how to use it
will reflect in the success of your business and can increase your earning potential
on cam. So there's lots of different ways that you can use the site either to promote
yourself or to build your brand. And if you really take full advantage
of all the ways to use it, then you can get more clients into your cam room and just
earn more in general. OK.
Did you want to talk through some of this too?
If you want to hand that to me, please do.
I'll just go through some profile maintenance.
So your profile is the first thing your clients see before they even see you.
So this is why we need to make sure it's the very best that it can be.
This is very important. We recommend updating your profile regularly, and
below are some suggestions for your profile.
So yeah, like when you first start, obviously your profile will be quite basic, and
that's fine. And then you can just keep adding to it all the time.
And then as you change on cam and you start to figure out what you really like and
what you want to do on there, you can write up your profile to match this.
And here is an example of our lovely mentor, Sami's profile.
She's got a lot on there, so we thought we'd use a picture of hers.
Because as you can see, she's got loads of different tabs.
She's got a lot of text. Her profile picture is great because she's like, really,
you can really see her in the shot. This is actually probably a perfect example of
what to use as a profile photo. And that is very important
because before they even see your profile, they just see the photo, just a small
photo, and then they'll click into that photo to then see the rest of your profile.
So nailing your profile photo is very important.
So yeah, I'll go through some of the things that you can add.
So you can add a wish list. This is obviously where you add items on there for
clients to buy for you. And whether it ends up being a successful wish list or not,
as in whether people are buying stuff off there for you every day, I think it's still
worth having stuff on there like this because it just kits your profile out more.
But if it's not there, then they can't buy you it.
So you may as well have it on there because you never know.
You might get a regular who really wants to spoil you.
So yeah, so that can be added onto your profile quite easily.
I think it's good to say as well that if they buy you something off your wish list,
they don't get your address, do they? They send it through AdultWork.
So you don't need to give them the address to have a wish list.
Yeah, exactly. So they'll just buy it, whatever it is.
And then you've already put your address in there for AdultWork to know where to
send it. So they won't see it, like Elle just said.
As it works, just automatically send it to whatever address you put in there.
So the next one is content to sell. Now I
feel as though I looked at this recently and maybe it's, you can't do that anymore.
I'm gonna have to, as we go on favour in the call when you're speaking next Elle,
I'm gonna take a quick look and don't know.
I've got a feel as if it's not there anymore but there's always other ways to sell
content as well whether you can put it on your profile or not because if you're in
a chat room with one of your clients and they wanna buy a pair of your stockings,
for example this is something quite popular that people like to buy.
You can just have them tip you however many credits you want for the stockings and
for postage. And then obviously ask for their address and then you can send it onto
them. So that's a way to sell content without it actually being on your profile for
sale. So if they've taken that feature away there's still a way to do that.
Another thing you can add to your profile is blogs.
So yeah, just another thing on there for clients to read a little bit more about
you and what you've been up to or whatever.
Some people write like erotic blogs or write about like sexy moments
in their life or whatever they write that on their blogs.
You can also add an introductory video. So maybe just a little movie
on your movies section, just maybe it could be a free one because
with your movies you charge the clients to view these, but maybe
you could just have one on there that's a very low charge or maybe even free just
so they can get a feel for you because your mannerisms and how you talk and stuff
like that is very different to just one photo.
So maybe they'll see this video and they'll want to see more.
And another good thing to put onto your profile is to let your clients know when
you'll be online. One of our girls actually does this religiously.
I always see that she's got her times on there.
She's been with us for a long time, like five, six years actually since way
back when. And she always writes every single time like she's going to be online
like Thursday, Friday, Saturday, 11 p.m. Till 1 a.m.
Or whatever it is. Like every week, like an update to every week.
And this works well for her because she absolutely smashes it on cam.
So I feel like she's got regulars that go onto a profile and then we'll say, oh,
she's not online today but I can see she's going to be online tomorrow at 11 p.m.
So then they'll make sure to then go back online at that time to see here.
So if you're someone who knows your schedule for the week or
the month or whatever then it would definitely be worth writing it on.
I know for a lot of people, they just go online randomly as and when and that's fine.
Obviously you wouldn't write it on your profile then.
But if you know, then you may as well because you never know who's watching your
profile and wants to cam you. G, sorry to interrupt.
Yeah, no, go ahead. We're not allowed to do that anymore, write on our profile what
times we're going to be online. No, okay.
Sorry, you can write, there's like a bit that you can write in what
you're available for. Like there's another tab or whatever it's called where you
can put your availability but you're not actually allowed to write that on your profile
anymore. I got a warning about it the other day.
So yeah, I'm not allowed to do that anymore.
That's what I mean when we say it changes all the time.
It's, you know, keeping up with it is hard, isn't it?
And all you do is just literally get like a little flash up, you know, like a pop
-up box to tell you that this has changed and then that's it, you don't see it again.
So it's so easy to miss them kind of things as well.
Yeah, you're not allowed to write that anymore.
So you have to put it in the proper, that if you go on my details, click on
my details, it will be on there. It will be on that screen, enter.
Yeah. Edit profile screen, yeah. Yeah, but you're not actually allowed to put it
on your profile anymore, it's just so annoying.
Thank you for sharing that. Okay, no worries.
Okay, so yeah, so just ignore everything I said, girls.
Okay, okay, so another thing you can add is an intriguing slash eye-catching bio.
So yeah, like again, this is something that the clients are gonna see before maybe
they even see you or maybe they come with you and then think, oh, I wanna know more
about here and then they'll go read your bio.
So what we always say with this is think about the client that you want to attract
and write your bio for them. So yeah, if you want someone
who's gonna be a bit more submissive or something like that, then you
would write, you know, a bio of like explaining how you're a dom and stuff like
that. Or if you wanna just be more like the girl next door, maybe you'll write that
you're new and you're excited to get started and you're just figuring all this out.
And you know, like just really think about what story like you're trying to tell
and what type of person you're portraying and then write that in like, write that
in your bio. And we actually have training on this, like on to
help you develop your bio. So just ask if you need any help or anything like that.
We also have some sheets as well actually, some like training sheets that help you
like break it down and like basically help you write out your whole bio.
You can also do the FAQs on the website. This is quite as quick, simple, easy one
to do. And it just adds another tab on your profile and more for the clients to explore.
So I'd recommend doing that. Oh, sorry, that's not a tab.
That's actually at the bottom of your profile.
So if more, if people are asking you the same question over and over, like you can
even have it on this, I suppose I'm sure it might be okay.
You could say like, what times do you go online?
Cause you can make your own FAQs and then maybe you could write it in there but I'll
have to double check that one. But it could be things like, yeah, you could just
basically if people are asking you the same question over and over, you can just
have it on your profile instead. And then you can also
add interviews. This is what I was meant to say just then about the tab.
So this creates another tab on your profile.
So the interviews can go from really simple ones like what is your star sign?
What is your favourite colour? But then as you get into it more, there's more like
questions that require more of a complex answer.
For example, some of the questions could be like, describe your ultimate sexual
fantasy or something like that. You have them type of questions.
So again, think about your webcam persona and fill out the interview as you're
being here or as you're thinking like she would.
Another thing that we recommend you doing as well quite often, cause the rest of
the stuff that I've spoken about here, it's kind of stuff that you'll do.
Like, you won't be doing it every single time you go online, you won't be updating
the interviews every time or writing a new blog every time.
This is just something you do every so often to build up the profile.
But one thing that we do recommend doing quite often is editing
your tagline. So the tagline is basically when
the clients are on the main webcam page of all the other members on there, when they
scroll over each member, their tagline will appear.
So it's just a small little phrase just to try and draw the clients into
your chat room that day. So you could write that you've got a new underwear set on
or that you're feeling really naughty today or whatever it is, you just write a small
little phrase in your tagline so the clients will see this and then hopefully click
into your cam room. So yeah, so we recommend updating that often maybe every
time you go online. And another thing to think about editing as well and we can every
now and again is your webcam price. So the website just goes
up and down over the year with how busy it
is. So sometimes you'll notice it's really, really busy and you're getting so many
clients often and this is where you either wanna keep your prices as they are or
maybe even up them a little bit because if the demand is there, then why not have
your price a little bit higher and make as much as possible.
But then maybe you'll notice it's not as busy at the moment.
So then in that moment I would probably lower the price a little bit, your price
per minute because then if it's a little bit lower and
it's not as busy, then it's probably a little bit more of a competitive rate.
So yeah, so that's something to look at depends on how busy you are and how busy
the site is. And of course, what clients are coming into your room as well.
So sometimes I would have a client who every time he come into my room, I would always
up the price because I knew that he would pay more.
So I'll just up it for him. So like if he'd email me saying, oh, I'll be online tomorrow
or whatever time, I would just up my price per minute a little bit, just a little
bit so they don't even notice, you know what I mean?
And then you're getting a little bit more.
So yeah, you can edit your price whenever you like.
And also your category. So when the clients go online, they
can just look at all the women online, or they can actually select certain
categories to only look at the members in each category.
So for example, there's categories that go through age.
So from teenager all the way up, like, you know, like 20, 30, 40, 50, like all
the way up. But then there's also categories that subdivide each kink
and fetish. So doms, subs, horny housewives, like, you know,
there's all different ones. So if you are a more fetish-based profile, sometimes
you might just wanna be in your age category, or sometimes you might wanna be in
the fetish category, or you might wanna try a new fetish, or then put yourself in
a different fetish category you'd never normally be in.
So that's something you can do as well. And finally, you can link your social media.
So they'll only accept certain ones, cause I tried to link my Instagram recently,
I think it was, yeah, and they wouldn't accept that, but they do normally accept
a Twitter. So if you have a Twitter account for your webcam persona, you can
link this. And to be honest, if you are serious about this and you're
common quite often, like, you know, part to full-time, I would recommend having a
Twitter for your profile, because on Twitter, you can actually meet a lot of clients
on there as well and direct them to your AdultWork, because Twitter is the place
where, it's the place where these guys go to find new
girls, like to find new people to come with.
Yeah, of course they go on the site to find them, but they'll follow the girls on
Twitter first and start to be like, oh, I really want to see her on cam.
And then they'll post their cam link and then they'll, you know, they'll go to them
through Twitter rather than finding them on AdultWork first, if that makes sense.
So I know a lot of girls don't want to show their identity, which is fine.
So you could even just have the Twitter and never show your face on there and just
show pictures of your, like, you know, just from the neck down or whatever else,
or even just pictures of your legs or sit in part of your body that you wouldn't
be able to tell it to you. And then you can link your AdultWork to
your Twitter and vice versa. So yeah, it's just another way just to put yourself
out there and be seen to more clients, because Twitter is the hub for sex work.
Instagram, probably not so much. They ban it a lot more, whereas yeah, Twitter is
definitely the place for that. So yeah, that's just some things that you can do.
Just to kit out your profile a little bit more.
I feel like the more that is on there, it makes you look more established and more
like professional, say, to the clients. So they believe that they're really common
with someone who knows what they're doing.
So yeah, I'll pass you back to Elle for the next slide.
Thank you. So business builder feature. So all
of the things that we talked about on the last slide are you can do all, make all
of those edits to your profile and things by logging in to AdultWork, clicking the
tab at the top that says my details. And then from that screen, you'll see edit profile.
So click edit profile, and then you'll be able to make any of those changes that
we just talked about. Obviously you can speak to your mentor if you're not quite
sure, or you want a bit of extra help. But then there's also from the my
details screen, there's the business builder feature.
So you'll see right at the bottom of that screen, there'll be a thing that says business
builder. And sometimes it will come up with a little red sentence in red
about how you could improve your profile.
So yeah, if you click on business builder from the my details page on AdultWork,
it will give you tailored advice on how to make the most of any features that you
haven't used yet, such as the various ways of promoting yourself, movies, blogs,
et cetera, along with tips on how to improve your earnings.
So it is actually quite good. I have been on this, clicked on it a few times.
If it says that there's an improvement I can make to my profile, because sometimes
it will be like something new that's come in or a new feature, and it will come
up with a little advice thing and you click on it and it talks you through how to
do it. And yeah, so it's quite a useful tool that you can use.
And I'll go through this shall I, cause then those.
Lot that you just went through. So phone calls, SMS, and direct IM.
So these are different ways that you can use AdultWork to increase your earnings.
So different things that you can do, apart from cam, to increase your earnings.
So if you're not feeling like getting ready for webcam, but you still want to earn
some money, you can try phone calls, SMS, or direct IM to bump up your earnings.
So phone calls and SMS chat. So what you'll
need to do for phone calls and SMS, again, if you log into AdultWork, I
think there's a tab, isn't there, that says phone chat.
Or if you go onto the My Details page, you'll see there, there's a bit that says
phone chat. So you click on that, and it will walk you through how to do it.
Again, you can ask your mentor if you need a bit of extra help with it.
So what you'll need to do for phone calls and SMS, so text chat, you'll need to verify
your phone number on AdultWork. Clients will not receive your phone number,
so they call you through AdultWork, so it's completely safe.
Unless you pay, which is a little checkbox, unless you tick the box to pay to display
your number on your profile, which some people do, but we do recommend just
doing it through AdultWork so that nobody's got your phone number.
It's a great way to keep in touch with regular clients to let them know when you're
online. And you can also build just a bit more of a relationship with them as well,
you know, if you're speaking to them on the phone as well as on cam.
And credits can build up fast with little effort required.
So obviously, you know, we all want to kind of get ready and look a bit sexy and,
you know, get into our character for cam.
But if you can't do that, which obviously we can't always do that, then phone calls
and text chat can be a good way to do it.
And you can even do it if there are other people around you, of course, because you
can't cam with people in the background or people in the room, but you can be texting
someone, you know, and that doesn't matter.
Direct IM. So Direct IM is the same as camming, you just don't have
your camera on. So it's just the typing in the group as you normally would,
but without the without the camera so they can't see you.
So understandably, you'll have to lower your price for Direct IM because they're
not seeing you. So they're not going to want to pay as much just to type to you.
But it can be a good way to just bump up your earnings and just to log on, you know,
on a whim, you know, if you don't want to get ready or you're somewhere that you
can't cam from. So to do that, you just need to switch on your Direct
IM from the webcam settings page. And remember to lower your price per minute.
Your mentor can show you how to do that if you're not sure.
But you just go on to, again, click on my details, click edit profile, and then click
webcam settings. And from that page, it's just a checkbox so that you want to do
Direct IM. Yeah, so you can do that from anywhere.
So you don't have to have your hair or makeup done or whatever.
It's an easy one to throw on and a few extra credits while lounging at home or on
public transport. Although, you know, we have also cammed from public transport.
So as long as you're sneaky, you can do that as well.
But yeah, just some extra ways to earn a bit of money.
And if you need any support with any of these, you know, some of our members use
them more than others. I am not someone who's used them an awful lot.
But we can always put you on to someone who has if you want to have a chat with them
and ask any advice. Do
you want to do this one? Oh,
let me unmute. Sorry. I forgot I was muted.
Okay, so being productive while waiting for calls.
Instead of just sitting around waiting for someone to call you, there are many things
you can do while you wait that can make a big difference to how busy you are.
So first thing you can do is to email everyone in your inbox telling them you're
online. I feel like this is like such a good thing to do because you've already got
in your inbox, you know, so many clients in there.
So yeah, I feel like it's a really useful thing to just go through them all or as
many as you can, you know, in the timeframe that you've got.
And just email them all back, whether, you know, you're double emailing them or not,
like who cares, like just, just send out the email.
You know, even some of them you might not have spoken to in months or maybe even years,
but there's still like a name in your email box that you can still access.
So I would still email them and just be like, hey stranger, how are you being?
You know, it's been such a long time, I miss you, let's catch up.
I'm online today, I'm online tomorrow, like, you know, whatever it is, and I'm going
to be online every day this week, like hopefully we'll get to catch each other.
So yeah, so it's just, you know, maybe if you send out 50 emails and only a small
percentage of them actually end up coming into your chat room, it's still something,
you know? So, and get you back on your client screens and get them seeing you again,
whether they come you in that moment or whether they see it, like the next week that
you're online and then come you then or whatever.
I definitely think this is a very useful thing to do.
I always do this every time I've not been online in a while and I'm back, I always
email everyone because then like they see that you're back online again.
Another really productive thing to do is to leave feedback for all your past calls.
So if you click on emails and bookings on the website at the very top
on that, like the top tab, you just click the emails and bookings, it comes up with
a pop-up screen that says some of your clients want you to leave feedback, so it
reads something like that, and then you just click okay.
And then it comes up with a list of all your previous clients and
like a little box for you to leave feedback for them.
So you can leave like, I think it's positive, neutral, negative, and then like a
little write-up about them. So obviously I always just select positive, obviously,
unless they've not been a good client, but to be honest, I probably wouldn't leave
bad feedback. I'd rather just report them just because if you were leaving bad feedback,
maybe they're going to then see that and then in spite leave you bad feedback, which
you don't want. So if there was ever anyone that I actually did have bad feedback
for, instead of doing that, I just report them to the AdultWork and get them blocked
off the site. But that's not going to happen often, to be honest.
So yeah, so when leaving feedback, obviously I always click positive and then just
write a little sentence in there. If you remember something about the chat or the
client, it'd be a good idea to write this in just so the client thinks, oh wow,
she remembered me, she remembers our session, and that goes the longest way.
So it's always good to make a little note when you're on each call, especially the
guys that are spending a lot, the guys who are in your chat room for a while, definitely
make a note about what they're into, who they are, like what you spoke about, how
the session went. And then you could mention something about this when you leave
your feedback. It's good to do this because the feedback means
that your profile is shown more across the website because then you're on their page
with the feedback so more people are going to see it.
But also, like I said, it just builds a good relationship with your clients and
it doesn't take long to do. And you don't always have to write something specific
to each client. You can just write a general one like, oh, I had so much fun, can't
wait to come to you again, or can't wait to chat with you again, or whatever.
And then when your client sees this, they're like, oh yeah, we did have fun, and
then they come to you again. You know what I mean?
So definitely worth doing this. Another thing you can do is to take pictures and
videos of your profile. So while you're dolled up, like sitting, waiting on cam,
if you've actually made an effort that day and you feel good in yourself, then why
not take a few photos and videos? And these can make you money.
If you take ones that you put into your private gallery, then you can actually, the
more photos you have in there, the more you can charge.
So you might take an extra 10, 20 photos and then you can bump the price up by a
credit or two because you've got way more photos in there.
And the same goes for videos. You can sell all your videos as well.
So you can record videos while you're waiting, put them up on your profile, and then
they're always there then for life or for as long as you want them to be making you
money. So yeah, this is definitely something you can do while you're waiting for
calls. Another thing that you can do is if you're just sat around and you just want
to be on cam, you don't want to be, you know, you've already done all the other things.
You've emailed everyone back, you've left feedback, you've taken photos, but you're
like, right, I just want to come with someone now and start making money.
You can turn on your... Your free chat. So the free chat, of course you're not making
money in free chat, but the good thing about it is it bumps your profile up to the
top of the website. So you're visible for more people.
And then of course, you're going to get a lot more people entering your chat room.
Because it is free, you will get an influx of people in there.
So just be aware of this. They don't ring you like they do on a paid chat on
group or private, they just pop in. So you don't have to accept them and they just
can go in automatically. So just be aware of that.
And of course, you will get a lot of freeloaders in here.
So just be ready for that. Just be ready that
people in there are going to be asking for stuff for free and probably a bit annoying
because you know they've got no credits because it actually tells you if they've
got credits or not. So just be ready for that.
But on the flip side, there is benefit to this because some of our girls love using
free chat because it bumps them up to the top of the page.
They get a few clients in there, maybe a few they just, you can just ignore that
ones that are just trying to be freeloaders.
You don't have to respond to those, but you will get some in there who are just coming
in just to see how you are. Maybe they're seeing if they can actually see you properly,
if your webcam's a good quality, this, that.
See if they have a good rapport with you and then they'll take you into a paid chat.
So this is why you use free chat. It's always just to get them in in the beginning
and then obviously to then persuade them to take you to a paid chat.
So you can do this because if you're like sat around waiting for calls because you'll
definitely get a lot of people in your chat room as soon as you turn on free.
And then you just got to make sure then to just turn it back off whenever you want
to turn it off. You just do it in your webcam settings.
So you go to my details, edit profile, click on the webcam tab, and
then you click on edit direct cam settings and a box will pop up.
The top left-hand corner is the box that you want to select, which says that you'll
do free chat. There's one on the right, which you don't want to select because that's
guest free preview. I wouldn't select this one because this just means that people
who aren't even registered on the site, they can preview you for free.
I wouldn't recommend that one. But if you just click the top left-hand corner box,
which says free, you want to do free chats, you could say how long do you want the
clients to be in your room for, for free.
So maybe you're only going to give them five minutes for free or 10 minutes.
And yeah, I wouldn't give them much more than that, to be honest, because if they're
not going to pay after that amount of time, then you don't want them in there much
longer than that. So yeah, you can tweak the settings to exactly how you want them
to be. And you just have to make sure to turn it back off again when you're done
with it. Another good thing to do to be productive is
to get ready to bid for the next hour. So I always recommend setting
alarms because you might think, oh yeah, I'll just remember at five minutes too,
but then maybe at five minutes too, you're in the kitchen or you're on a call or
whatever, and you just forget to bid for that next hour.
And then when it locks out, you haven't done it.
And then you've got another whole hour where you're not on the front page.
So yeah, you can always just set an alarm at five minutes to the hour to remind yourself
to bid for the next hour. And now it's made a lot simpler because they have a boost
button right on your direct cam page on the page that you're streaming on.
So you can just click the boost button when it's like five minutes to the hour and
then put in however many credits you need for it to go green.
And then once it goes green, you'll know that you're going to be on the front page
for the next hour and hopefully be very busy.
So another thing that you can do as well is to take a look at the client's connection
page and message potential clients and send flirts.
So I feel like this is something we've actually not even spoke about before, I don't
think, but it's a very, very useful tool.
So on the client connection page, you can actually reach all of your clients you've
come with and also search all of the clients on the website.
So you've got access to message. Well, in the beginning, actually, you can't message.
You have to send a flirt in the beginning, but you have access to send a flirt to
literally all the clients on there. Of course, you'd be there all day doing them
all. You'd be there for days doing them all.
But if you've got 20 minutes while you're waiting for a call, just go on there and
send as many flirts as possible. Then hopefully that'll translate into a paying client.
So you're You'll see what I mean when you take a look on there, but sending a flirt
is just something like, you can blow someone a kiss or I don't know, just something
like this, it's just like a little message that it sends to the client.
And then once you've sent the flirt, after that, it then gives you the option to
message them, so that's great as well. You can message brand new clients and just
be like, hey, I'm online, I don't think we've met before.
You know, it would be fun to get to know each other or, you know, I'm feeling really
frisky today or I'm feeling really submissive today or, you know, whatever it is
that you want to present yourself as that day, you can let the clients know.
So yeah, I think this is a really good page for people to really take advantage of.
And another thing to do while being productive while you're waiting for calls is
to update your profile or tagline. So as we spoke earlier, there's a lot to do on
the profile and it always needs updating.
Even when you've got a really, you know, amazing kitted out profile, there's still
always more you can add or tweak or change and doing this regularly really helps
as well because it helps bump your profile up to the top of searches.
So yeah, when you're sat around waiting for calls, you might think, you know what?
I'll just take a little look at my profile now and see what I can add on there.
So yeah, there's so much you can do. I know what it can get like when you're just
sat around and no one's calling and you're like, oh, what's going on?
And you start to think, you know, you start to think the way it's like, you know,
am I ever going to get any calls again? Like, you know, is this it now for me?
Like I've had all these thoughts before, trust me.
Or maybe you're not, maybe you've got a great attitude and you never think that way,
which is great. But I know that it can be easy to start to think like, you know,
start to have like a negative spiral with your thoughts if it's not so busy.
So doing these things while you're sat around waiting, it's going to like take you
away from that mindset and it's actually going to benefit you so much because everything
like we've mentioned here, it's going to benefit you no matter what because like
emailing people back or bidding for the next hour, like all these things, it's proven
that it works. It might not work every single time for every single person,
but I believe that it does most of the time.
So yeah, so it's definitely worth, instead of just sat around like, you know, wondering
when you're going to get another call, be proactive and do the things that we, you
know, will get you those calls. So yeah, that's what I'd recommend doing there.
And I'll pass you on to Elle for the next slide.
Thank you. Okay, so Lovense. So this is very new,
isn't it? This is like the newest feature on the site.
For those people who use toys, this is an amazing thing that they've added.
So yeah, let's chat about the renowned Lovense toys.
So many of our members have found success with the Lovense range and earned hundreds
of credits just in tips alone. So yeah, we've seen a few members doing really well.
I know I've had a couple of my girls messaging me that they've done really, really
well with the Lovense. So yeah, for anyone that does do this kind of thing, I think
it can be really lucrative and a good thing to set up on your profile.
So you need to install the software. So once you've done that, it will
show as a widget on your live cam page. You can then
send your client a link. So a client gets a link to control the toy and you can decide,
I think you can decide how long for and the intensity that they can
control it for. When a client tips, the toy
will vibrate. So you can set how many credits, that's right, for how long and what
intensity. And of course, it's up to you how
you're going to use this feature. But I know that some of our members have had the
toy just next to them on the bed, so you don't necessarily have to have the toy inside
you or be using it properly, it's part of the
act, isn't it, part of the performance. So it's up to you how you display that and
up to you how you do that. Obviously, even with a toy, it's
still in the selling, isn't it? It's still in the alert, it's still in the tease
and in the story. It's not just like wham bam and a little vibrate
because it's in the communication where you're going to earn the money and drawing
the people in. So you can also link it with music,
which I didn't actually know. And I think that's amazing that you can link it with
music. And your cam screen lets the clients know that
you have a Lovense toy. So if you're not in the mood to use it on any given day,
make sure to disconnect it so that that widget will not be there and other people
won't be able to see that. I think it's also a really great thing.
If I'm, I don't know, correct me if I'm wrong, but when you're
on FreeChat, they can see that you've got the Lovense toy.
So is that right? I think I'm pretty sure that's right.
So then even just going into FreeChat is like a real good advertisement, isn't it?
Because if they can see that you've got that, obviously they're gonna wanna cam with
you a million times more if they know that you're using that.
And they can even just tip you from there.
So yeah, it's a really great thing to earn some money.
I think some of our girls have done really well with it.
And it's a really good boost when you've got a new thing that you can use and then
you earn a load of money from it. It's just a good confidence boost as well, isn't
it? It makes you wanna get online even more.
So yeah, that's still relatively new. So if anyone wants more information on that
or help with it, just let us know and we can help you.
But yeah, the girls that I've been using them, I've been raving about it.
They could literally just make hundreds of credits just in tips because the more
they're tipping you, the more it's vibrating or whatever else it brings the toy alive.
So yeah, if toys are something that you use on cam, this toy will probably pay itself
10 times over straight away. So it's definitely worth looking at that.
Yeah, and there are so many ways that you could incorporate that into your cam persona
as well as in like, if you're submissive, you can work that into like what the guy's
doing to you or if you're dominant even, it can be a reward that they can tip you
so much and you can tell them how much to tip.
You can work it into what you're doing, can't you, in the conversations you're having,
which is good, I think. Okay, and
then so a little bit about what to do when you have any issues.
So of course, we're all gonna get tech issues now and again.
Some of the time that's gonna be about our own stuff, like our own systems or WiFi
or whatever else. Sometimes it's gonna be about the site.
When the site is having updates, there can be some, it can get a bit annoying tech
-wise, there can be some issues. Generally, if we know that there's an update and
if we know that there are issues, then we'll post about them, but we don't always.
So what to do when your cam isn't working.
So usually restarting your laptop or computer and clearing your internet history
does the job. Remember, it helps not to have other windows open or
other things running on your device. So this can really impact the quality of your
connection and just make it drop out or whatever.
It's also worth having a look at what you're using, what
browser you're using, cause sometimes different browsers work better with different
devices. And I know for instance, that on my laptop, Firefox
always works better for me than Internet Explorer or other things.
So yeah, just having to play around with what works best for you.
Yeah, if these things don't help, then there are occasional issues with the website,
particularly during updates, as I just said, which can cause issues.
Sometimes we just have to be patient until it's fixed.
And of course we can use that time to work on our profiles or do a load of the stuff
that we've just mentioned. So yeah, just making sure that we use that time well and
don't get too disheartened about it cause it can happen now and again.
And of course, if there's like issues with the website or you're having some problems,
then if you've got phone chat or text chat or whatever set up, then it's something
that there's also, as a backup, isn't it, something else to rely on.
So you know you can still do something. What to do when things go wrong.
So if anything goes wrong or you have any issues and you're unsure, speak to your
mentor straight away or post in the group and one of us will get back to you and
we'll look into it for you. So please don't try and fix the issue yourself as sometimes
it's a simple fix on our end. So for example.
For example, sometimes if you haven't been on for a while, they may
sometimes remove your services. So they may say, you know, if you haven't webcammed
for ages that you need to go through an extra check in order to cam again.
Or just little things like that. Sometimes it's much better for us to send a message
or to sort it out from the group rather than you do as an individual.
So if you have any issues with getting on cam, then just speak to your mentor.
If it's something that you can do, then your mentor can let you know and you can
do it. But if it's something that's better done from our end, then we'll handle it
for you. Also, don't panic if, you know, there are so many rules and the rules
are changing all the time. So if you accidentally break a rule that you weren't aware
of, then sometimes you can get a warning or
they can temporarily remove your profile or delete it.
But we can 99% of the time get it back. So for instance, one of the girls had like
her cat walked across the back while she was coming.
She didn't realise that that was not allowed.
You can't have anyone else in the back of your cam, including pets.
So something like that, you know, she went on to cam the next day and her profile's
removed. So there's a big panic about it.
But we can sort it, we can get the profile back and figure out what's gone on.
So if there's anything that you're panicking about, anything like that happens, just
let us know and we can message for you. Is there anything you'd add on
that? Yeah, I was just going to say, because sometimes as well, you could incriminate
yourself. I remember it happened, she was like, oh, you know, it might
have been because of this, because I let my friend be on there or something like
that. And her profile was put on pause, say for example, for another reason, it wasn't
anything to do with that. And she was literally about to send an email like, I'm
so sorry, I didn't mean to let my friend be on there, blah, blah, blah.
I was like, no, no, no, no. Let's not incriminate yourself here.
And it actually wasn't even about that. It was something else, a very minor thing.
And we got the profile back so easily. So I was like, I'm so glad that you didn't
send that email because then she literally incriminates herself because it wasn't
even about that. And they never knew about that until she would have told them about
that, you know. And we have a good relationship with ads at work as a group.
So even if there's some issues that you wouldn't be able to fix on your own, they
will fix them for the group, if that makes sense.
Because they're like, oh, yeah, let's say, for example, your profile needs to be
re-verified and you don't have the correct document to verify it.
You're trying to do it on your own with the incorrect documents, not going to work.
Whereas if we say, oh, we know this isn't the correct document, but on this one occasion,
can we just re-verify it with this? They're more likely to do it for the group rather
than for the individual profile. So because we have a good relationship with them,
it's always better for us to sort out all the issues.
So, yeah, just reiterating what you said there.
I'll just never panic. Maybe don't try and do it yourself in the beginning.
Always just ask us and then we can say, oh, yeah, it's actually just you just tick
this box. That's all you do next time or whatever.
It might be something as simple as that, or it might be that we have to actually
put in a form and contact them and stuff like that.
And so, yeah, just always check with your mentor and never panic.
But yeah, basically what you just said, Elle.
But I just wanted to say, like, yeah, just be careful because, you know, you could
actually incriminate yourself and you don't want to do that.
Yeah, I remember that moment recently when she was going to just send all this.
It could be this or that or this. I was like, oh, my God, no, don't tell them you've
done all this stuff. OK. Do
you want to do this, Jane? OK, so managing your
credits. OK, so when you want to check what you've made, always use the
credit statement page to check your credits.
Don't just go off what it says on the live cam page as this doesn't account for fees
or credits used on positioning. So when you're on cam, obviously, it has a little
thing in the corner that says how many credits you're on.
This isn't a true representation because as I've just mentioned there, there are
small fees that get taken off from every single call.
It's called a faculty fee. And it's like, you know, probably like 0.2 credit or whatever.
A very small amount that gets taken off each call.
But of course, that adds up over time, like, you know, over that cam session.
So that page doesn't account for that. And also when you're bidding every single
hour to be on the front page. Whether it's three, four, five, six credits, it also
doesn't account for this. So if you're online for like four or five hours and you
bid every hour, that could be like 20, 25 credits that you've used that it's not
accounted for. So you might think, oh, I've earned 300 credits, but you forgot about
the 25 that needs to be taken off from the position and then also all the faculty
fees. So there may be, it's not actually 300, it's actually 270, but you've
got on your head, oh, I've made 300. And then that doesn't, and then the next day
when you get paid, you've got paid a lot less than what 300 credits would work out
as. So then you're like panicking, like, oh, you've been underpaid or whatever.
But usually it's just because you're looking at the wrong page.
So if you go to the credit statement, so you hover over my details and
then click on credit statement. And then in there, it's your full credit statement,
which is completely accurate. So in there you can work out exactly what you've made.
I'm gonna talk through it now, but we do have videos as well on the members area
on the week one of the welcome course, which shows you exactly how to do this.
I would recommend sitting down with your laptop or computer, whatever, and the
video on one side of the screen and then have your credit statement on the other
and just follow through the video and follow the steps that we say and work out how
to work out your credits. So what you do is you,
so let's say, for example, I wanna see how many credits I've made today.
What I would do is I'd go to the very last transaction of today and see how many
credits are there. So let's say it says 190.
And then you go to the very first transaction of the day and see how many credits
are there. Because just because your credit statement says 190, it doesn't mean you
have 190 credits. That's just how many are in your credit statement at the moment.
Okay, so yeah, so it ends on 190 and let's go to the start of the day and it will
say, let's say it says 100. So you started the day with 100 credits in
your account and you ended with 190. So to work out what you made that day is
you subtract the 100 from what you started on from 190 and then that shows that you
made 90 credits in that day. So then once you've got how many that you made, so you've
made 90 credits, you then need to translate that into pounds.
So what you can do is you can just write it into your calculator.
So 90 take away 43.5 and then click the percent sign and that'll show you
how many you've made or you can just write it in your calculator and times it by
0.565 because this accounts for
all the fees that are taken. So there's a fee to be a part of this agency.
There's a fee to be on the AdultWork website and there's also a very small fee for
the payroll company that pay you daily. So yeah, so that's how you work out
how to translate it into pounds. And finally, if you ever think that your pay is
wrong if you've worked out and you still believe that you've not been paid correctly
which does happen sometimes our payroll company it's not an automatic, you know,
it's not a computer they're humans. So they do make mistakes every so often but everyone
is always paid everything they're owed. So if you are noticed a mistake, if you are
noticing that your pay has been wrong one day just let your mentor know we will contact
payroll straight away. As soon as they've seen that there's a mistake you'll get
paid the difference. So yeah, so that's how you work out your credit statement.
Like I said, it might be a little bit easier to sit with the video and just go through
the video step by step and you can literally pause it and be okay.
So first of all, do this, pause, look, do that and then, you know, do every step.
And once you've done it a few times yourself you will get used to how to work it
out. In the beginning, it will look a bit overwhelming.
And you'll be like, what, how do I work this all out?
You know, all these different transactions and it just looks a bit, looks a bit,
yeah. It just looks a lot in the beginning, to be honest.
But once you've done it a few times, you'll be fine.
And if you never learn how to work it out that's also fine because that's what we're
here for. So yeah, that's how you check your credit statements.
So that brings us to the end of the PowerPoint.
And yeah, I know that that's been maybe a lot of information,
just thinking. In. So we have recorded this call and we'll put it up on the site
on the members area so you can have a look back at it if there's anything that you
want to look back over but also all the stuff that we're talking about and much much
more is on you know the courses on the site and on the other training videos and
on the training that you'll get with your mentor and things so yeah there's there's
lots of other places to look for this information and you can always ask us any questions
and but does anyone does anyone have anything they want to ask right now you know
either about what we talked about or anything else to do with AdultWork no
okay well you know our doors are always open you can always message us on you know
in the group or via WhatsApp and either your mentor or us we're happy to answer
any questions so yeah yeah
of course just about obviously everything you're talking about is to do mostly to
do with the main the desktop type site and one of my new girls has only got her mobile
phone and on she's been on the website a little bit and obviously the mobile site
is a lot more simplified but it is still complicated but you can get on the desktop
site and it's harder so you know go through the video it basically you've
only got one device it's harder to do things but you know just to reiterate that
you know we're all here for as well I'm on the mobile site a lot so I can pretty
much navigate that and she's in Liverpool as well so AdultWork won't get too angry
about the different locations because we're practically in the same location so she's
in this call so just to let you know don't worry about anything and mobile
sites are fine as well um but yeah that was it really I literally
always click to go on the desktop version of the site even if I’m on my phone because
I just think it's so much easier to just be working with that version and I used
to always do that and then everyone was like the app the app the app and I was like
I hate it but then eventually I was like oh it's quite simple but it's
just once you get to know it isn't it it's um not as overwhelming but it is a horrible
website when you see it for the first time yeah yeah definitely yeah
well it sounds like you're the perfect person to help with that anyway so yeah
mobile site is yeah I know what's not on there if you know what I mean
yeah yeah that's what I found because it was a bit more simplified it was hard to
harder to find things that I wanted to find yeah well it maybe it's a better start
to start with that anyway yeah we'll see yes
okay thank you so much thank you for coming everyone and
you know spending a bit of time to think about you know putting some time into this
um and yeah hope to see you all very soon
okay thank you thank you